skinnyms.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy

**SKINNY MS WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY**

**Effective Date: June 1, 2018**

This website, located at www.skinnyms.com, as well as all services related to this website (collectively, the “Site”) is provided by Skinny Ms, LLC, a Tennessee Limited Liability Company (herein referred to as “Skinny Ms”, “we”, “us” or “our”).   This Privacy Policy, along with our Website Terms and Conditions apply to Your visits and use of our Site. Any information that you (hereinafter “You”, “Your” or “User”) submit to the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Modifications**

Skinny Ms reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy, with or without notice, at our sole discretion. Therefore, it is recommended that You regularly visit this page and familiarize Yourself with the latest version of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Site will signify Your acceptance of any revised Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise stated, all amended terms shall be effective upon posting to our Site.

**Privacy Statement**

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways we treat personally identifiable and other information about You and Your computer, mobile or other device when You access, visit and/or use the Site. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites, applications, destinations, or services linked to from the Site.

**Type of Information We Collect**

  1. **Submitted Information.** The Site generally collects personally identifiable information with Your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when You enter a sweepstakes or contest, complete a survey, make a purchase, subscribe to our publication(s), register for certain services, or register and/or set up an Account to access, visit and/or use certain portions of the Site, or the Site as a whole, You may be provided, or required to choose, a password and/or User ID, and You may provide a credit, debit, or charge card number, or other payment information, as well as Your name, telephone number(s), email and/or street address, and other personally identifiable information. Other information such as Your age, gender, an avatar, and the number for Your mobile or other device may also be requested. In addition, You may be asked to send us similar information via messaging (e.g., email, SMS, MMS, or other technologies). All such information shall be referred to in this Privacy Policy as Your “Registration Information”.
  2. **Browsing**.  If You browse through the Site without entering any personal data, we may automatically gather and store certain information about Your visit. Our servers may also automatically collect information about You, Your online behavior and Your computer, mobile or other device. The information collected may include, without limitation, the make, model, settings, specifications (e.g., CPU speed, connection speed, browser type, operating system, device identifier) and geographic location of You and/or Your computer, mobile or other device, as well as date/time stamp, IP address, pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, the site(s), application(s), destination(s), and/or service(s) You arrived from, and other clickstream data.
  3. **Social Media Information.    **If You choose to access, visit and/or use any third party social networking service(s) that may be integrated with the Site, we may receive personally identifiable information and other information about You and Your computer, mobile or other device that You have made available to those services, including information about Your contacts on those services. For example, some social networking services allow You to push content from our Site to Your contacts or to pull information about Your contacts so You can connect with them on or through our Site. Some social networking services also will facilitate Your registration for our Site or enhance or personalize Your experience on our Site. Your decision to use a social networking service in connection with our Site is voluntary. However, You should make sure You are comfortable with the information Your third party social networking services may make available to our Site by visiting those services’ privacy policies and/or modifying Your privacy settings directly with those services. We reserve the right to use, transfer, assign, sell, share, and provide access to all personally identifiable information and other information about You and Your computer, mobile or other device that we receive through third-party social networking services in the same ways described in this Agreement as all of Your other information.

**Cookies other Tracking Technologies**

  1. **Cookies.**  A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about You may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.  We use cookies for the following purposes: (a) authentication – we use cookies to identify You when You visit our Site and as You navigate our Site; (b) status – we use cookies to help us to determine if You are logged into our Site; (c) personalization – we use cookies to store information about Your preferences and to personalize the Site for You; (d) security – we use cookies as an element of the security measures used to protect user accounts, including preventing fraudulent use of login credentials, and to protect our Site and services generally; (e) advertising – we use cookies to help us to display advertisements that will be relevant to You; and (f) analysis – we use cookies to help us to analyze the use and performance of our Site and services. 
  2. **Google Analytics**.  We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our Site. Google Analytics gathers information about Site use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our Site is used to create reports about the use of our Site. Google’s privacy policy is available at: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).  
  3. **Refusing Cookies**.  Most browsers allow You to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:

(a) [https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en) (Chrome);

(b) [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences) (Firefox);

(c) [http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/](http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/) (Opera);

(d) [https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies](https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies) (Internet Explorer);

(e) [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411) (Safari); and

(f) [https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy) (Edge).

Please note that blocking cookies may have a negative impact on the functions of many websites, including our Site. Some features of the Site may cease to be available to You.

  1. **Other Tracking Methods.** In addition to Local Device Storage, we may use web beacons, web bugs, clear gifs, and similar technologies (collectively, together with Local Device Storage, the “Tracking Technologies”). We use Tracking Technologies for all or some of the same lawful business purposes we describe above for use of Local Device Storage.

**Third Party Tracking Technologies**

Our advertising service vendors and other third parties will at times also use Tracking Technologies to serve You advertisements tailored to interests You have shown by browsing on this Site and other sites, applications, destinations, and services You have visited, and to determine whether You have seen a particular advertisement before to avoid sending You duplicate advertisements, and for other lawful business purposes. In doing so, these third parties will collect non-personally identifiable data including for example the make, model, settings, specifications (e.g., CPU speed, connection speed, browser type, operating system, device identifier) and geographic location of Your computer, mobile or other device, as well as date/time stamp, IP address, pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, the site(s), application(s), destination(s), and/or service(s) You arrived from, and other clickstream data. The use of Tracking Technologies by third parties is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy, and we have no responsibility or liability in connection therewith.

**How the Site Uses and Shares Information About You**

  1. **Processing Requests.** We use personally identifiable information You supply through the Site to provide You with the merchandise, product, service, and/or content You have requested. For example, if You subscribe to any of our publications, we may use Your e-mail address to send You a confirmation notice and Your mailing address to send You the publication. Similarly, if You enter an online sweepstakes, we will use this information to notify You if You are a winner. We may also use the information to communicate with You about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to Your needs.
  2. **Sharing Your Information**.   Unless otherwise specified on the Site, we may sell or share information about You and Your computer, mobile or other device, including without limitation Your Registration Information and other personally identifiable information, with our parent, subsidiaries, and affiliates and with carefully selected companies who we think may offer services and/or products that may be of interest to You. If You do not wish to have Your personally identifiable information shared with third parties, contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as described at the end of this document. If You do not wish to receive future commercial messages from us, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the message You receive. (But note that You may continue to receive certain communications from us, such as transactional or relationship messages, and/or messages about Your account/profile). If You’ve registered on any part of the Site, please use the mechanism or contact information on the Site that allows You to change or update Your member preferences or information, if available, to keep all such data accurate and up-to-date. If no such mechanism or contact information is available on the Site, contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as described below with Your changes.
  3. **Advertising.**  This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.  By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners.  You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).  However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.  
  4. **Maintenance and Processing.** We may also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, market research, community and forums management, auction services, and shopping, personal/job search and other classified ads functionality, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. And if You choose to purchase merchandise, products and/or services, including without limitation content, on or through features on the Site, we may forward Your information to third parties for services such as credit card or other payment processing, order fulfillment, credit pre-authorization, and address verification. There are also times when You provide information about Yourself to us in areas of the Site that may be managed or participated in by third parties. In such cases, the information may be used by us and by such third party(ies), each pursuant to its own policies. We may also provide Your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to You that meet Your needs or match Your interests. While we may seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.
  5. **Public Interest**.   We reserve the right to access, use, and share with others Your personally identifiable information for purposes of health, safety and other matters in the public interest.
  6. **Legal Investigations.** We may also provide access to our database in order to cooperate with official investigations or legal proceedings initiated by governmental and/or law enforcement officials, as well as private parties, including, for example, in response to subpoenas, search warrants, court orders, or other legal process.
  7. **Geographic Location**. **   **In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about Your computer, mobile or other device (including its geographic location), which may at times be able to identify You, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, analyze trends, track users’ movements around the Site, and to otherwise administer the Site. Geographic location information about You and/or Your computer, mobile or other device may specifically be used to show You content and sponsored messaging based on geographic location.
  8. **Aggregation of Data**.   We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any lawful business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers, sponsors, clients and customers. We also reserve the right to identify You from Your Registration Information and/or to merge or co-mingle anonymous or non-personally identifiable data about You, Your offline and online behavior, and/or Your computer, mobile or other device (including its geographic location), with Your Registration Information and/or other personally identifiable data for any lawful business purpose.
  9. **Acquiring Parties.** In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by us, our parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Site users may be among the transferred assets.

**Transfer of Information**

Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, servers and databases located outside of Your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as Your jurisdiction. Please be advised that we may transfer Your information to and from any state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction, and process it in the United States or elsewhere to the extent permitted by law. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your submission of such information represents Your agreement to any such transfer.

**Information Security and Notification**

  1. **Not a Guarantee.** Because no data transmission is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of the information You send to us or the security of our servers, networks or databases, and by using the Site, You agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when You access, visit and/or use the Site, including without limitation Your personally identifiable information or other Registration Information, and we are not responsible for any loss of such information or the consequences thereof.
  2. **Not Responsible for Your Devices.** Moreover, if You elect to store information, such as Your personally identifiable information or other Registration Information, where others may access it, we are not responsible for any loss of such information or the consequences thereof. If You lose a computer, mobile or other device, or it is stolen, that contains Your personally identifiable information or other Registration Information, it is up to You to take all the steps necessary to protect Yourself.
  3. **Notification**.  In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of Your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify You. If notification is appropriate, we may notify You via Your computer, mobile or other device.

**Kids and Parents**

This Site is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to register for the Site or provide any personally identifiable information or use our social, community and public discussion areas, photo and video galleries, bulletin boards, forums, chats, blogs, and other ads, and elsewhere. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17, inclusive, must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this Site. If Your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Site, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, You should tell them not to do so. If You’re worried about Your children’s activities or their privacy on the Site, we encourage You to contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as described below.

**European Economic Area Residents**

  1. If You reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws You have the rights, among other things, to access Your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If You wish to access or delete Your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, You can contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If You wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track Your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. 
  2. If You are a resident of a country in the EEA, You have the rights, among others, to:  

  1.     1. access Your personal data;
    2. ensure the accuracy of Your personal data;
    3. the right to have us delete Your personal data;
    4. the right to restrict further processing of Your personal data, and
    5. the right to complain to a supervisory authority in Your country of residence in the event that data is misused.

If You believe that our processing of Your personal information infringes data protection laws, You have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of Your residence, Your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.  You may exercise any of Your rights in relation to Your personal data by written notice to us addressed to the following: 

Privacy Policy Coordinator  
14 Fair Oaks Road  
Crossville, TN 38572  
contact (@)skinnyms.com

**Notice to California Customers – Your California Privacy Rights**

California’s “Shine the Light” law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the business’ practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. We have such a policy in place. As discussed above above, if You wish to opt-out of our sharing of Your information with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes or to find out more about Your opt-out rights, please contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as described below.

**Privacy Policy Coordinator, Opt-Out Requests and Other Privacy Questions:**

If You have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, please feel free to contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as follows:

Privacy Policy Coordinator  
14 Fair Oaks Road  
Crossville, TN 38572  
contact (@)skinnyms.com

You may opt-out of having Your personally identifiable information shared with third parties for their marketing purposes. If You wish to exercise this right, please contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator and state that You want to opt-out of our sharing with third parties. If You wish to request updates or changes to Your information or Your preferences regarding receiving future promotional messages from us, You may contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator.
